One word can change everything.
Yes Man is a comedy, romance film directed by Peyton Reed.
Carl Allen, a guy whose life is going nowhere, signs up for a self-help program
based on one simple covenant: say yes to everything…and anything.
Carl Allen, played by Jim Carrey.
Renee Allison, played by Zooey Deschanel.
Peter, played by Bradley Cooper.
Nick, played by John Michael Higgins.
Norman, played by Rhys Darby.
Rooney, played by Danny Masterson.
Yes Man is a 2008 romantic comedy film directed by Peyton Reed, written by Nicholas
Stoller, Jarrad Paul and Christofer Tufton, and starring Jim Carrey.
The film is based loosely on the 2005 memoir of the same name by the British
humorist Danny Wallace, who also makes a cameo appearance in the film.
Production for the film began in Los Angeles in October 2007.
It was released on December 19, 2008, in the United States and was then
released in the United Kingdom on December 26, 2008.
The film received mixed reviews, with most critics calling the plot too similar to one of Carrey's
past films, Liar Liar, but was a box office success, making $223 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of california, bungee-jump,
falling in love, ex-wife, hollywood bowl.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.